Privacy – BubbleTree USA                                                                     

On-line purchasing temporary unavailable

 D86E1719-CE18-4FD8-98AC-9087382DA577@2x

Privacy
=======

American Bubble Company LLC Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from [www.bubbletreeusa.com](http://www.bubbletreeusa.com/) (the “Site”).  Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use the Site. By accessing or using this Site, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of this Site after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates. 

INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU AND HOW WE COLLECT IT

We may collect several types of information from and about users of our Site, including information:

* by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address or telephone number ("**personal information**");
* that is about you but individually does not identify you; and/or
* about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Site and usage details.

We may collect this information:

* Directly from you when you provide it to us.
* Automatically as you visit, interact and navigate through the Site.

INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO US. 

You are not required to provide personal information. We will only collect such information when it is voluntarily provided to us on the Site, by email or through some other format. The information we collect on or through our Site may include:

* Information that you provide by signing up to receive our emails.
* Information that you provide when placing an order.
* Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.

Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies**.** 

As you navigate through and interact with our Site, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

* Details of your visits to our Site, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Site.
* Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, Internet Service Provider, platform type, referral source, and browser type.

The information we collect automatically is statistical data and does not include personal information, but we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Site and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

* Estimate our visitor size and usage patterns.
* Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Site according to your individual interests.
* Recognize you when you return to our Site.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

* **Cookies (or browser cookies).** A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Site.
* **Web Beacons.** Pages of our Site may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Association, for example, to count users who have visited those pages and for other related Site statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain Site content and verifying system and server integrity).

We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here:  https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/.  You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here:  [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

* To present our Site and its contents to you.
* To provide you with information or services that you request from us.
* To fulfill any orders for which you provide it.
* To notify you about changes to our Site or any products or services we offer or provide though it.
* For any other purpose with your consent.

DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We may disclose personal information that we collect, or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

* To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our Site or business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them. For example, we use Shopify to power our online store--you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy.
* To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it, such as to add you to our mailing list.
* For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.

We may also disclose your personal information:

* To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
* If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of us or others.

We do not sell, trade, or rent any personal information to others.

IP addresses are unique numeric identifiers that are assigned to each browser accessing the Internet. An IP address, by itself, cannot identify you personally. However, when combined with other information provided by your Internet Service Provider (ISP), your IP address can be used to identify the computer accessing the Site. Under certain circumstances, recipients, their legal representatives, and/ or law enforcement authorities may be able to combine this with information disclosed by ISPs to determine the source of a particular communication. By using this Site, you knowingly and voluntarily assume any risks associated with such disclosure. 

CREDIT CARD INFORMATION

If you make a purchase through our Site, we may collect contact information (such as name physical address, email address phone number), in connection with your purchase.  We do not process any underlying payment facilitated by the Site; payment is processed by our payment partners, currently we use Shopify and PayPal ("Payment Partners"). Credit Card information that you input to consummate a transaction is encrypted using SSL technology. Only the Payment Partners may be given access to the full credit card number that you provide. We do not have access to your full credit card number, although we may access or store the last four digits of the Credit Card number for record keeping purposes. Data handled by a Payment Partner is subject to that Payment Partner's terms and privacy policy.

DATA SECURITY

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure.  Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Site. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site.

DO NOT TRACK

Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

THIRD-PARTY LINKS AND SOCIAL NETWORKING SERVICES

Our Site may include links to third-party websites, plug-ins and applications. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their privacy statements. When you leave our Site, we encourage you to read the privacy policy of every website you visit.

The Site may include links to or integrate with social networking services. You understand that we do not control such services and are not liable for the manner in which they operate. While we may provide you with the ability to use such services in connection with our Site, we are doing so merely as an accommodation and, like you, are relying upon those third-party services to operate properly and fairly.

You should be aware that information which you voluntarily include and transmit online in a publicly accessible blog, social network or otherwise online may be viewed and used by others. We are unable to control such uses of your information, and by using such services you assume the risk that the information provided by you may be viewed and used by third parties.

EUROPEAN USERS

If you are an individual in the European Union, we collect and process information about you only where we have legal bases for doing so under applicable EU laws, including the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”).  The legal basis may depend on the type of information and how you use the Site.  If you have consented to our use of information about you for a specific purpose (for example if you make an order through the Site), you have the right to change your mind at any time, but this will not affect any processing that has already taken place.  Where we are using your information because we have a legitimate interest to do so, you have the right to object to that use though, in some cases, this may mean no longer receiving communications or utilizing certain features on the Site.  We are not required to have a data protection officer, so any questions about our use of your personal data or related requests should be addressed to: [info@americanbubble.com](mailto:info@americanbubble.com)

YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

If you are a California resident, California laws, including under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 may provide you with additional rights regarding our use of your personal information. To learn more about your California privacy rights, see below:

DATA RETENTION

When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13

The Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 13. We, therefore, shall not intentionally collect information about any user under the age of 13.  If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Site.  If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [info@americanbubble.com](mailto:info@americanbubble.com)

CHANGES

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons. If we make material changes to how we treat our users' personal information, we will notify you. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the bottom of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

CONTACT US

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at info@americanbubble.com or by mail using the details provided below:

For California Residents

American Bubble Company LLC (“we,” “our,” and “us”) is furnishing this additional information to natural persons residing in the State of California, as required by the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (the “CCPA”). This information should be read together with our Privacy Policy. https://american-bubble-company.myshopify.com/ABCPrivacy

This CCPA supplement to our Privacy Policy is dated and effective February 1, 2021.

The CCPA requires certain disclosures that already are covered in our Privacy Policy. https://american-bubble-company.myshopify.com/ABCPrivacy This section provides additional specific information required by CCPA, including information about how to exercise your rights under the CCPA.

The CCPA permits natural persons who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, a list of the third-parties to whom we have disclosed their Personal Information (if any) in the prior calendar year, as well as the type of Personal Information disclosed to those parties. We do not sell, rent, trade or share Personal Information with third-parties for their own marketing purposes.

We do not sell your data. We only disclose Personal Information to unaffiliated third parties as set forth in this Policy. You have the right to request information from us regarding whether we share certain categories of your Personal Information with third parties for our marketing purposes. To the extent we share your Personal Information in this way, you may request information related to (i) the categories of information we disclosed to third parties for such purpose during the 12 months and (ii) the names and addresses of third parties that received such information.

Disclosures About the Sources and Uses of Personal Information

As described in our Privacy Policy, in order to provide the Services, we may have collected Personal Information from several categories of sources in the past twelve months.

This includes several categories of Personal Information as defined by the CCPA:

* Identifiers, such as name, postal or electronic address and telephone numbers;
* Personal information as defined under the California Customer Records statute (California Civil Code § 1798.80(e)) such as contact information;
* • Commercial information, such as transaction information and billing and payment history;
* Internet or network activity information, such as browsing history, interactions with our website, and Internet Protocol (IP) location;
* Geolocation data, such as device location and Internet Protocol (IP) location when you interact with our website;

We use your Personal Information for a variety of business purposes, as explained in the Privacy Policy. https://american-bubble-company.myshopify.com/ABCPrivacy

In order to provide the Services, we may share Personal Information with others. We never sell your Personal Information. During the past twelve months, we may have disclosed, for a business purpose, information within the categories listed above. See our Privacy Policy [https://american-bubble-company.myshopify.com/ABCPrivacy](https://american-bubble-company.myshopify.com/ABCPrivacy) to learn more about the categories of Personal Information we disclose, and the categories of third parties to whom your Personal Information is disclosed.

1. Your Rights

California residents have the right to:

* Know your Personal Information. The CCPA permits users of our services who are California residents to request and obtain from us twice a year, free of charge, information related to Personal Information we have collected in the 12 months preceding the request, including the categories of Personal Information collected, the categories of sources from which the Personal Information is collected, the specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected, the business or commercial purpose for collecting Personal Information, the categories of Personal Information that we disclose to third parties and the categories of third parties with whom we share your Personal Information. See further instructions for receiving your Personal Information, below.
* Delete your Personal Information. You may request that we delete the Personal Information that we have collected from your use of the Services. We will delete your information unless it is necessary for purposes permitted by CCPA. See further instructions for deleting your Personal Information, below.
* Opt-Out. The CCPA gives you certain rights to opt-out of the sale of any of your Personal Information. Since we never sell, rent or trade your Personal Information, you need take no further option to opt-out from the sale of your Personal Information.
* Consent to new uses. Before we use Personal Information for any purpose not previously disclosed to you, we will notify you of this new use and obtain explicit consent from you to use it for this purpose.
* Non-discrimination. If you choose to exercise any of these rights, we will not deny services to you or provide different quality of services, unless that difference is reasonably related to the value provided by your data.
* Authorize an Agent. You may designate an agent to make a request under the CCPA on your behalf. To do so, please provide the agent a written letter appointing the agent, acknowledged before a notary public. The agent must furnish a copy of the appointing letter to us when taking action under the CCPA on your behalf. You may also point an agent using a power of attorney pursuant to California Probate Code, Sections 4000 to 4465.

To request information about your own Personal Information, including information about the categories and specific pieces of information collected, or to request that we delete your Personal Information, please contact us at the contact information shown below. Please provide your name, email address, and any other information which you believe will help us to locate your records.

We will not furnish Personal Information to anyone unless their identity has been verified to a reasonable degree of certainty or, in the case of sensitive or valuable Personal Information, to a reasonably high degree of certainty. We will not provide consumers with specific Personal Information if the disclosure would create a substantial, articulable and unreasonable risk to the security of the Personal Information, the consumer’s account with us, or the security of our business systems.

American Bubble Company, LLC

325 Larchmont Blvd. Suite 230

Los Angeles, CA, 90004

Attn:– CCPA Requests

800-484-4325

American Bubble Company, LLC

325 Larchmont Blvd. Suite 230

Los Angeles, CA, 90004

United States

Last Revised:  January 22 2021

#### Customer Care

#### @Bubbletreeusa

* 

© 2021 American Bubble Company LLC, All rights reserved.  
Products available in the contiguous US

* Choosing a selection results in a full page refresh.
* Press the space key then arrow keys to make a selection.
